Orb
محجر العين
Why are you so stupid
لماذا أنت بهذا الغباء
Without you
بدونك
So what if I survive
فماذا لو بقيت على قيد الحياة
Why hasn't Shu De come back yet
لماذا لم يعود شو دي بعد؟
Big princess is not good
الأميرة الكبيرة ليست جيدة
Lou Guifei is here
لو جيفي هنا
Just say Shu De sleeps late and stop her quickly
فقط قل أن شو دي تنام متأخرًا وأوقفها بسرعة
It's too late
لقد فات الأوان
Mother Shu De has come to see you
لقد جاءت الأم شو دي لرؤيتك
Open a country princess
افتح أميرة البلاد
It's late in the morning and don't get up yet
لقد تأخر الوقت في الصباح ولم تستيقظ بعد
What does it look like
كيف تبدو
Sister Huang, I've taken care of it
الأخت هوانغ، لقد اهتمت بالأمر
Mother concubine
أم محظية
I won't say anything
لن أقول أي شيء
She knows everything
انها تعرف كل شيء
How about Jin Jiu
ماذا عن جين جيو
Has been safely out of the palace
لقد خرج بأمان من القصر
You let the prisoner die privately
لقد تركت السجين يموت على انفراد
He's not a prisoner
انه ليس سجينا
He is someone I care about very much
إنه شخص أهتم به كثيرًا
Absurd
سخيف
A humble grass-raiser
مربي العشب المتواضع
How can you be confused with the princess
كيف يمكن الخلط بينك وبين الأميرة
Mother concubine
أم محظية
I took Jin Jiu out of the palace
لقد أخرجت جين جيو من القصر
Confused
مشوش
Your Majesty must not know about this matter
جلالتك يجب ألا تعلم بهذا الأمر
Sit down
اجلس
Shu De released prisoners privately
أطلق شو دي سراح السجناء على انفراد
Ruler twenty
الحاكم العشرين
Sentenced to the Imperial Mausoleum for one year
حكم عليه بالضريح الإمبراطوري لمدة عام واحد
Father, emperor and son know that they are wrong
الأب والإمبراطور والابن يعرفون أنهم مخطئون
Father can't, Your Majesty can't
الأب لا يستطيع، جلالتك لا يستطيع
Your Majesty, the orb is your daughter
صاحب الجلالة، الجرم السماوي هو ابنتك
Shu De is also your daughter
شو دي هي أيضًا ابنتك
How can you favor one over the other
فكيف يمكنك تفضيل واحد على الآخر
It was my idea to let Jin Jiu go
لقد كانت فكرتي أن أترك جين جيو يرحل
Shu De was coerced into helping by me
تم إجبار شو دي على المساعدة بواسطتي
If you want to punish her, punish me first
إذا كنت تريد معاقبتها، عاقبني أولاً
It's nonsense
كلام فارغ
Let him go
دعه يذهب
You're dying
أنت تموت
Father
أب
I don't have much time
ليس لدي الكثير من الوقت
Why do you have to risk Jin Jiu's life
لماذا عليك المخاطرة بحياة جين جيو
If you really think of your daughter,
إذا كنت تفكر حقا في ابنتك،
Just let him go
فقط دعه يذهب
Leave him alone
اتركه لوحده
This is the Jin family owe you a life
هذه عائلة جين تدين لك بالحياة
You care so much about Jin Jiu
أنت تهتم كثيرًا بجين جيو
It's just that he cheated me and made me feel better
إنه فقط أنه خدعني وجعلني أشعر بالتحسن
Orb
محجر العين
Father won't hurt you
الأب لن يؤذيك
Jin Jiu, that boy
جين جيو، ذلك الصبي
He can't be trusted
لا يمكن الوثوق به
To my daughter is to like him
لابنتي أن أحبه
I forbid you to hurt him
أنا أمنعك أن تؤذيه
Sister Baozhu
الأخت باوزهو
Sister Huang
الأخت هوانغ
Bearer
حامل
Bring Princess Baozhu back to her bedroom
أعد الأميرة Baozhu إلى غرفة نومها
Strictly guard
حراسة مشددة
Don't step out of the bedroom again
لا تخرج من غرفة النوم مرة أخرى
Notify the Dark Guard
أبلغ الحرس المظلم
Make every effort to arrest Jin Jiu and return to the palace
بذل كل جهد للقبض على جين جيو والعودة إلى القصر
How dare you come here
كيف تجرؤ على المجيء إلى هنا
Why don't you dare to come
لماذا لا تجرؤ على المجيء
Do you know who you are now
هل تعرف من أنت الآن
I should be the one who deserves
يجب أن أكون الشخص الذي يستحق
Wanted man with a national reward
مطلوب رجل بمكافأة وطنية
You're not looking for me
أنت لا تبحث عني
To help you escape
لمساعدتك على الهروب
I really came to ask you for help
لقد جئت حقا لأطلب منك المساعدة
But not running away
ولكن ليس الهروب
Take me to the palace
خذني إلى القصر
How dare you come back
كيف تجرؤ على العودة
Are you really not afraid of death
هل أنت حقا لا تخاف من الموت؟
Of course I'm afraid
بالطبع أنا خائف
Who is not afraid to die
من لا يخاف أن يموت
Especially when you have someone you care about
خاصة عندما يكون لديك شخص تهتم به
Your Majesty treats the princess like a pearl
صاحب الجلالة يعامل الأميرة مثل اللؤلؤة
In your capacity
بقدرتك
It won't work out with her
لن ينجح الأمر معها
I didn't expect the dark guard
لم أكن أتوقع الحارس المظلم
It turned out to be a pedantic person with a family concept
اتضح أنه شخص متحذلق ذو مفهوم عائلي
How does the stockade leader see you
كيف يراك قائد الحظيرة؟
Gentleman talks but doesn't start work
الرجل يتحدث لكنه لا يبدأ العمل
I still want to see Baozhu
ما زلت أريد أن أرى باوزهو
You're gonna hurt me
سوف تؤذيني
It's time for her to be sad
لقد حان الوقت لها أن تكون حزينة
I admire your courage
أنا معجب بشجاعتك
It is worthy of being after the Jin family
إنه يستحق أن يكون بعد عائلة جين
If you can survive this time,
إذا كنت تستطيع البقاء على قيد الحياة هذه المرة،
I believe in the capital
أنا أؤمن بالعاصمة
There must be a place for you
يجب أن يكون هناك مكان لك
Are you soliciting me
هل تطلب مني
I'm from Naihe Village
أنا من قرية نايهي
Be careful to go back
كن حذرا في العودة
The stockade leader asked you to kneel and rub the clothes board
طلب منك قائد الحاجز أن تركع وتفرك لوح الملابس
To survive
البقاء على قيد الحياة
There is hope
هناك أمل
Your Majesty Jin Jiu brought it to
صاحب الجلالة جين جيو أحضره إلى
Your Majesty
صاحب الجلالة
Young people don't know the rules
الشباب لا يعرفون القواعد
There will be a price to pay
سيكون هناك ثمن يجب دفعه
This is your majesty's rule
هذه هي قاعدة جلالتك
It is the rule of the world
إنه حكم العالم
But I just want to play by my own rules
لكني أريد فقط أن ألعب وفقًا لقواعدي الخاصة
Keep watch over the people I care about
أراقب الأشخاص الذين أهتم بهم
Spend one's life
قضاء حياة المرء
I heard you came back by yourself
سمعت أنك عدت بمفردك
Are you really willing to sacrifice everything for the orb
هل أنت حقاً على استعداد للتضحية بكل شيء من أجل الجرم السماوي؟
Since I chose to come back,
وبما أنني اخترت العودة،
You won't leave her
لن تتركها
You can only delay her toxicity
يمكنك فقط تأخير سميتها
But it can't save her life
لكنها لا يمكن أن تنقذ حياتها
Even if it's just to delay her for a little longer
حتى لو كان فقط لتأخيرها لفترة أطول قليلا
I'm happy too
انا سعيد ايضا
Jin Jiu
جين جيو
I don't have to kill you
ليس من الضروري أن أقتلك
Not just for the orb
ليس فقط من أجل الجرم السماوي
But as a father
ولكن كأب
Thank you for your affection for Baozhu
شكرًا لك على محبتك لـ Baozhu
Your Majesty
صاحب الجلالة
It's the birthday of Baozhu soon
إنه عيد ميلاد Baozhu قريبًا
I hope you can make her happy
آمل أن تتمكن من جعلها سعيدة
Twentieth birthday
عيد ميلاد العشرين
I don't know next year
لا أعرف العام المقبل
Orb
محجر العين
I'm back
لقد عدت
You can't poison me
لا يمكنك أن تسممني
But I hope you can live to be seven or eighty
لكني آمل أن تتمكن من العيش حتى السابعة أو الثمانين
By the way, keep my share alive
بالمناسبة، حافظ على حصتي حية
To live to be twenty is a lifetime
أن تعيش حتى العشرين هو عمر كامل
Living to be eighty is also a lifetime
إن العيش حتى الثمانين هو أيضًا عمر كامل
As long as I can be with you
طالما أستطيع أن أكون معك
One second at a time
ثانية واحدة في كل مرة
It's all a lifetime
كل ذلك مدى الحياة